The hair diwan one second Welcome to The
Amazing and through this previous video we are going to
learn that the training app which is the
feedback here you
can use the pipe, we are going to
see it with the heart, which light bills are going to be
needed for this and what other things are
needed, all those things today we have told you from the heart,
but first I will tell you where to use this face
tips, where should you use it,
but before that I will explain that thing to you, if the
secondary school remains closed
then I will show you here, there is
PIMS, you will see it there, so like
here you can see your system, inside this system
also you can see Edison and secondly
see, you pick up any mobile, have tea, pick up
brother's phone, whoever is
yours, but his husband, then the
December which you use, there is
vibration spread over the human sapta dhatu,
like here through my system I will
tell you that there is print, where will I see it, so
here I open the camera, open the camera,
you have a good camera this time,
see, till now the hair pack is made which is on the
tree  As I am calling, the
face that is
Paris Jackson's Juice
Raghavan has to be deficit reduction, so
if you want to follow this pattern,
how can this pattern be made today,
we will search for it, so for now, I will
ignore that
I have not given it so much time, through which we will explain how to make it,
now for this, first of all we
need our library,
using which library can we make this pimple,
then you will get a sharp edge, so
what you have to do
here, at the top
where you find it, you have to click on
this video,
now you have to touch this video, the power of
videos related and images Oberoi,
touch it image processing time above it, of the
spirit of etc. of Kalinga, everything
can be done here, now how to
take the time, so meet the person who
shows pizza open this topic,
go to the search box below, take
CMD here, you have to open chrome,
after opening chrome, command  This tip
install OpenCV which is your school,
what will happen with this is that this model of Open Sigra which is
available under modular operation is
my system, so the
code which I have already subscribed here will
not be rational, WhatsApp should be downloaded, in this
way what can you do here, by
submitting OpenCV next what do we have to do
so we have to write one and a half to two please don't do that let's
go to that Patkar has to
make the most of any party's penetration
which you have your own name, this
can be the problem of pillar, if you want you can work on someone else only,
like your tea
pure how to do the work here cursed life
first of all this
module of OpenCV you will have to do it,
those who want to improve its model name is
how CV now before performing here,
first of all we will ghee here our
camera, we will enable the camera of the lodge system
and after enabling the
video that is captured from it, our first work is
that dead skin, we will keep a physician here, so ah
here  We will do our
camera here to purify the ischemic rice,
first of all I have to turn on this camera,
so I have to capture this video, so
for this we will have to
create a camera and within a few minutes
we have many functions
inside any function, we have to email the video capture
function here, so
first of all what should I do,
create it here, through which now I will take beezon dot
here in the name of video capture,
which will enable our camera, now
if you want to call the runtime camera,
dance video kab tak dot co, you will have to use
this, welcome to the runtime half
camera, now I want this camera to be disabled
every time, just a particular
here on the Play Store availability, the
camera that you have here,
Karnataka, for that I will have to use
Wild here, so I
put Boil here and after that I put Choose
through which all your cameras will be
permanently through how you
use it to run the internet, if you do
not approve here then  This will keep going on, we will just do it
here, the files that are installed will come out
everywhere, one and a half 7 here, we give
these points, you do not press the button
or any treatment will come here from now on
you will see that this camera, this camera has a
good plug, the picture you
want, you will have to comment on this feature, if the
camera is done, but you
must Jimmy, tell me to do these images in the current as well, to
fix the images,
first of all you will need two Bibles here,
first of all I am going to
deposit the right hand side here, wow Banaras wow
cricket, I am making a planet here in the name of video,
which is this video
here, so for this I have put the
video here, how do you like the video, don't let this
images come here, I want to
tweet it, it is red color, now quickly
our target is here, these messages are there,
after being beaten, now I have to
start something, but to start
means memories, like if I go back here to the
camera, then the camera is made, then
I have avatar politics love,
this love increases  A
title is created which you can see here
another love is made in the name of camera, in
which this kind of cream is going on in my video,
we have to make 24
love here, so to make the cream
TV Tubelight here I will have to use the
items yes image has to be strengthened
so let's use chopan, it
will show now for this first of all I have to
give the name of the film, so I will give the song video in the name of video live here,
make a film roti in the name of live, play this new video here,
see what has to be done here
that this video which is captured and its
vinegar here,
after all how long will I sleep here in the name of video,
so I will give it here, hey let's work, it
makes a video in the name of underscore and teeja to
show it a little so that if there is any
problem then video and support
here you will answer the data, so this
video has come to us and they did not have it,
but now our video will have to be stopped sometime or the other,
so I will do the same, clash
Ghanshyam will keep going, so now to stop it
we will do it here  Let's click and then
I do it again and after applying this path the
TV which is here the date is
inside it what does the daughter of the stomach do
last week the images that images plugin which is the
camera now let's talk about the camera, this is about it it does for a
particular time it
means getting you shot
so it reaches inside the busy video
through wait key and tweet what can you do, you
can turn off the time playlist by reading any images so what I have done here is
this great key here
so that then the time generation will keep on going but
now we want that these images should be closed
when I one thing here
on the world of old age so for that I will use and d here for that
and I will
try at the time of this ward then I have
closed the images here
now
here
I have done one here
now after that you will have to use this video
so I will
use it here so that this is it now there is
a problem so
what will we do now so
this
video is live match  I like
all these things, after that
now make it strong here, so look on the glass there is a
close button and I have made the close button minister,
like in the name of Sanghati, this is
your video camera here, here it will go to
lip lock, so in this way you
can use it, what should be done in mobile,
definitely click to follow,
here I will do suicide and
these people are wearing similar dress, ok so close it, so in
this way you can call here,
next we have to make a video here,
till now we have come to the video that
we want to make, till now
we had a video that came to you and
we had seen it, you can show the live runtime video,
now what will be our next
that we want the video, this we were
not doing production or co-production, it was going on
normally, now whenever I
react to tuition fees, then friends to react,
first of all
I have to do those features from behind the face here,
now from where will this thing that is behind
come through the page, so for that I will
code you here  What do you have to do,
right now it is written, what do you have to do with it, I have
copied the link of the comment and placed it below,
so that if you do
not have the camera then you can take it
and now if you want to create a page, then let's
understand what is written in it, PS,
now this is your normal page here,
with more return maximum, if you have
this through what, pizza tears
lips, all these
things, what do you have to check all these things,
what do you have to do to capture these vegetables, you will
need the
PS classification of the house of intelligence here, if
they are cancer, then for this it will be
real, so I will fill in the name of press here,
please
subscribe here, now which here two
dot, what name do you have here, you will have to
use, so
subscribe 9 that
if we start all this, now
what will have to be done inside it, the
beta required for capture will be the data, now the
data is going to get work, so it will give, you
can also take it by typing name, if you want
visitors etc.  If you want to buy the book from the official website
or from the internet, then
you will be limited because the
first important thing is that you can get it from there.
Now where will you get this Chinese to file?
Generally, when you install the pattern here,
you will get the files of the camps there.
Like my digestion is that if you do not find this
retail finance recruitment notification here in the third section, then
you will have to
find the reader who is the update etc. shoulder, so
I opened it like this. Now
you do not have to fight with these people that
where did it start, so the written answer is
given here. When this program of D.O. was of
my stall, here is the complete
address. It is said that fry the C
so that now the gas pipe is important and you can also take this fort
to the site and go to the shop and you will find
this cv2 that OpenCV
installed here. So you can search it by going there. So
I will also
tell you that this which you mean the sun is
back with the neck straight, you will get it. So
I reached here on foot.  110 steps then
I go live after the place goes live
I am on the site where there is tight I go inside it and
double click here so the
thing that I have is their see Rashmi 210
setting I opened after opening this video
when you open the folder from Sabka then
after opening the depend folder here some xml file will go here
this xml file yours hear
define some code this is related to different price of
space
picked up this is
related to high quality part so now here you will
find facilitated search so look if you
search here then up is gas high cost is
here an asked is piece is related to this
now there is traffic point of front
process and here is bring to front
piece and look here at the point s
excel here below is your loot
which is related to stomach you will find things so
search this on full body if you
want to apply it on full body then you have to apply school thin
so for now you can take any of these  So what
I am going to take from this is
this one escetta front facial
deposit asset will be available so I will go
and this is not as much as I want I will just open it,
this is my requirement so
I will copy from it and
decorate my folder and put more on the messages this thing is
fiber I will also have to give the text of the bill
so I will go to the property here
after going to the property if you
keep this thing security forces
5003 without any part you
cannot do this work that this file is in any other folder
and this white bread is in the soft
either you take it and copy that point to fold
or you work directly
so I would like to work with the address in the plant I will
give that address here
and inside the address all the tempered
glass will have to be converted now
inside the crotch I want to wish the man a birthday I am
going to do that till the time I can do this word so
now I said take note of this
let's now this option of ours here
complaint is important  What next
now
our body part is
here, before that we have to
subscribe it is of
absolutely white color,
you have to wait a little here, here it is, so
for that after clicking
[music] here,
here
by the name of need which is
here,
use its husband red color and inside the CT color,
first of all I have to
change the color of the images, so I am that York's alam
this caricature, but now we have to change the color,
here my color here is converting it to green
color and we will click on it, at
that time the famous singer Sapna was that
means we will be
able to find out the body part, what will we do by fanning the color back, we will
write tight in color, so
for that we will sewage twice again and here
I will use color so that the color of I is
visible, so I have used color here, I have used color here,
I am using color here, we have to go to the previous,
after going to color it, you have to select
BGR to Bhringraj, for this you will
want multiple corrupt, press here, so
but we  We have to use the clutch that we want to do in the
middle, so yes now I will search here,
then you can easily say that
we should use grey color or black and white color,
if so now what do we do, let's do our
boxes for that, so
before preparing our pizza speech,
I will have to read the cover of the tractors,
so let's cover its success,
especially to call it, we will have to do something
like this, first of all we will have to
make a piece named bag, what is the doubt,
which is printed in the options and we have
not done chakli here, pimples and Belgium, we will have to edit it,
how much size should this song have, how many said
youth should we be here, now
we have to
increase the fold features of our Ghagra here and for this I will
need 4 minutes, half and so I am going to
give some of them here,
this parameter will be needed and from where will you
get this pitch, like a
specific one to apply this
Now put the here or between you don't here
we have the rating for it with your name only
we will keep it here with the name of it is dangerous
because on this only one makes you that
you must read now
click on this first of all you had to click on this
so I have cooked the video of DJ
which if you are reading you have to apply on it
check now
what all should be seen first of all its height of
birth the misfortune of the mobile and
x y z is included in it x
plus and w so this data you have
you have express w means I would like to
talk in express the
detox that data expressed regret
how should it look like the width okay and will
keep according to the white plus seat and the
color that is I am taking the color which
should be 225 on March 2018 and statement of
cost is needed just this we are here Anshwar
now what should I do let me run it by chatting
first of all turn on the video and
planets so that I please
subscribe so watch this my  The
video is good and I need a lot of support Ajay
that I have
happened to Prabhjeet make sure Manju Masood
everything is fine now I
refer this video here on the date and next
now I will raise you here tell me
Yogi frill is okay first of all
I like shared this video which your
spreading lies is written inside witch
chutney now I tell you here friends that the
recipe that you have used in your tweet,
what is it doing, the biggest which is
our caller video player, this video
completely in black and white color format
interval because our paste from Himachal
which is needed, means like in this, if I
talk about 20 here, then the age is let's
use it loop slow and keep all these things
on the capture length, so what happened
son, while doing this do Vijay and
note so that there is drinking water problem every thing
here we pause it black so next
you have here and now this innocently
he has covered in some specific room now to make
this very thing we have
locked it through this form, what did we do this
box youth  I have made this which is
responding to this green color, so it has
detoxed in the box, now where would I
find the chapter there and Tyothar it will
give till now below like I
see you this is access in this my voice this is my
wife and how high is the hybrid I have
decided I
need Vaikunth this box and how the graph is one and a
half so decide the boxing here and through
I am show we have to like this that here the
network software is prepared here
through the end key we have to wait for it and as I
press one like this the
mark problem of Puja is okay so in this way
and the program is here these people place here
you have the receiver here there is feedback
through which you can issue a press note here
now here the month in this so
how will he react to everyone and it is in front of you
because when come then you must have understood more
that the punishment has been made PM here
I have explained one by one all step by step 4
what should be the arrangement of Triphala Jio  let's meet
with our remedy don't
stay with us put it down do it
[music] it's
happened that
a